George Korson Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR148)
    - Side A
      - While The Union's Growing Strong
        Performed by Charles Langford
      - We Shall Not Be Moved
        Performed by Charles Langford and Owen C. Tolberrt
    - Side B
      - Union Boys Are We
        Performed by Charles Langford and Owen C. Tolberrt [?]
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR149)
    Original ID #4
    - Side A
      - Twill Be Sweet To Meet Mother
        Performed by John Cummings
    - Side B
      - The Reckless Moterman; Death of Rufus Miller
        unidentified performers
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR150)
    - Side A
      - Miners' Lullabye
      - Hard Toed Shoes
    - Side B
      - The Tenderfoot
        Performed by George Davis
      - Closed Shop Blues
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR151)
    Original ID #6. Unidentified performers.
    - Side A
      - The Harlan County Blues
      - Death of the Blue Eagle
    - Side B
      - The Spirit of ‘39
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR152)
    Original ID #7. Al songs may be performed by Cleveland Perry.
    - Side A
      - Introducing Song
      - Travelin' Shoes
    - Side B
      - Travelin' Shoes (last verse)
      - Union Solo
      - I Shall Not Be Moved
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR153)
    - Side A
      - You Can Tell The World
        Performed by Cleveland Perry
    - Side B
      - Didn't It Rain
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR154)
    - Side A
      - Union Boys Are We
        Performed by Marvel Quartet or Charles Langford and others - male vocal quartet
    - Side B
      - Keep the Union
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR155)
    - Side A
      - Didn't It Rain
    - Side B
      - Union Band
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR156)
    - Side A
      - Miners' Strike Song; The Strike Is On
    - Side B
      - Company Union Anthem; We Have A Union; We Are Growing
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR157)
    - Side A
      - John L. Lewis, A Fightin [sic] Man
        Performed by Henry Mayfield
    - Side B
      - United Mine Workers' Melody
        Performed by George Jones
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR158)
    - Side A
      - Stand Together
    - Side B
      - [Untitled]
        The word "void" is written on label, but the disc has four bands cut into it
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR159)
    - Side A
      - Coal Creek Rebellion
      - Tennessee Miners' Song
      - Down In A Coal Mine (variant)
    - Side B
      - The Miner's Lifeguard
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR160)
    - Side A
    - Hignite Blues
    - Coal Buckin [sic] Blues
    - Side B
    - Little Lump of Coal
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR161)
    - Side A
      - Paid Up Union Card
    - Side B
      - Don't Want To Work For Nothing
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR162)
    - Side A
      - Black Mountain Fire
    - Side B
      - The Hard Working Miner
      - The Mule Skinners' Blues
    - Coal Loadin' Blues
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR163)
    Original ID #18
    - Side A
      - We're Independent Now
      - A Little Mining Town
      - Pay Day At The Mine
    - Side B
      - Union Days Are Here Again
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR164)
    Original ID #19. All songs performed by George Sizemore
    - Side A
      - Drill Man Blues
      - Going Democratic
      - The Snitcher
    - Side B
      - A Miner's Life
      - In Harlan Town
      - Just Before The Union
      - We Need A Rest
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR165)
    Original ID #20. All songs performed by George Sizemore
    - Side A
      - Why Should We Scab?
      - True And Trembling Motorman
    - Side B
      - Miner's Lifeguard
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR166)
    - Side A
      - Tell the Operators
    - Side B
      - Wake Up Men
      - Better Run, Bill Green
  - Sound recording (musical performance), on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR167)
    Original ID #22.
    - Side A
      - Death of Mother Jones
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR168)
    Original ID #23. Songs performed by Quartet (United Four Quartet - Gus Jones [?] and other male vocal quartet).
    - Side A
      - Bill Green, Better Run
    - Side B
      - What the Union Has Done
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR169)
    Original ID #24
    - Side A
      - Don't Want To Go Down Yonder
        Performed by Quartet
    - Side B
      - It's John L. Lewis All The Time
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR170)
    Original ID #25
    - Side A
      - The Toilers
    - Side B
      - n/a
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR171)
    Original ID #26
    - Side A
      - The Miner's Cabin (My Mother Was A Lady)
    - Side B
      - Digging In The Barroom; Old Song
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR173)
    Original ID #28
    - Side A
      - The Young Lady Who Married A Mule Driver
    - Side B
      - The Mountain Miner
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR174)
    Original ID #29
    - Side A
      - Two-Cent Coal
        Performed by David Morrison
    - Side B
      - Red Necks
        Performed by Brown
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR175)
    Original ID #30. Songs performed by McGuire.
    - Side A
      - Chorus of Old Song
    - Side B
      - Chorus of Robb's Song; Variant: In The Barroom
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR176)
    Original ID #31. Songs performed by Mrs. Thomps. [Thompson?].
    - Side A
      - A Miner's Prayer
    - Side B
      - Don't Go Down in [the] Mine
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR177)
    Original ID #32
    - Side A
      - The Homestead Strike
        Performed by Haser
    - Side B
      - Marchesi; Group
        Performed by Fannie Sellins; Fannie Sellins
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR178)
    Original ID #33
    - Side A
      - Blue Monday
        Performed by Barry
    - Side B
      - P. Murray's Old Song
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR179)
    Original ID #34
    - Side A
      - Union Blues
        Performed by Russell Brown
    - Side B
      - A Coal Miner's Goodbye
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR180)
    Original ID #35
    - Side A
      - The Hard Working Miner
        Performed by G.C. Gartin
    - Side B
      - Brave and Trembling Motorman
        Performed by Stanley [Achenbach?]
      - Coal Diggers' Blues
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR181)
    Original ID #36
    - Side A
      - John L. Lewis Blues
    - Side B
      - It's On In Washington
        Performed by O.J. Jenks
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR182)
    Original ID #37. Songs performed by O.J. Jenks.
    - Side A
      - Little Lump of Coal
      - Union Coal Mines in the Sky
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR185)
    Original ID #40
    - Side A
      - The Dying Brakeman
    - Side B
      - Battle of the C.I.O.
        Performed by Evening Breeze Sextet
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR186)
    Original ID #41. All songs performed by O.J. Jenks.
    - Side A
      - The Lost Rib
      - No Lowdowns Around
    - Side B
      - Number Six Blues
      - Union Cannonball
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR187)
    Original ID #42
    - Side A
      - Goodwill Strike
        n/a
    - Side B
      - Bartley Mine Disaster
        Performed by the Evening Breeze Sextet
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR188)
    Original ID #43
    - Side A
      - Coal Miners vs. Coal Loading Machines
    - Side B
      - Union In My Heart
      - Cheer To The Union Travelers
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR189)
    - Side A
      - Interview with Betty Korson and Doris Sponsle
    - Side B
      - Interview
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR190)
    Disc is broken.
    - Side A
      - Soldier, Won't You Marry Me?
    - Side B
      - Marching Through Berlin
        Performed by Danny Botkin [Daniel Botkin]
      - The Field Artillery Song
      - The Marines' Hymn
      - Deep in the Heart of Texas
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR191)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
        Radio show segment with man talking about Congressional prayer groups, with stock music playing in background; Hop Up Ladies (fragments; song has mechanical dropouts); child singing; several children singing (song interrupted); unidentified man singing in an Irish brogue
    - Side B
      - Wild Rover
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR192)
    - Side A
      - Down in a coal mine
        Performed by Dan Walsh. See AFC 2003/011: SR117.
    - Side B
      - Miner's Jig Dance [clog]
        The dancer is Mine Superintendant Stewart. Accompanied by fiddle music. See AFC 2003/011: SR144. AFC 2003/011: SR125 may be the same performance.
      - The Miner's Last Refrain
        Performed by Dan Walsh. See AFC 2003/011: SR119-120, SR132, and SR144.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR193)
    - Side A
      - The Collier's Dying Child
        Recitation of a poem by an unidentified man
    - Side B
      - [Unidentified]
        A man speaks a few lines; possibly intended to be a letter or a message.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR194)
    Titles supplied by the AFC processor.
    - Side A
      - Johnny Sands
      - Willie the Weeper
      - The Famous Pig Song
    - Side B
      - [Unidentified]
      - The Red Coat [?]
      - The Hunters of Kentucky
        Also known as The Battle of New Orleans. The recording ends abruptly.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR195)
    - Side A
      - A Game Swap
        The title is unconfirmed. May be "Charlie is a Dandy."
      - Five Tinkers
        Children singing, with a man giving a spoken-word introduction
      - Shoot the Buffalo
      - Old Dan Tucker
        Children singing, with a man giving a spoken-word introduction. The recording ends abruptly.
    - Side B
      - [Unidentified]
        Unidentified man reading a story
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR196)
    - Side A
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [unidentified segment], circa 1949-1952
        Miss Roach testifying (?) about the mine workers welfare fund. Possibly part of "Labor and the Nation."
    - Side B
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [unidentified segment], circa 1949-1952
        John Herlin (?) interviews Mr. Hinton (a coal miner from Betsy Lane, Kentucky) and another, unidentified miner. Interviews took place at the George Washington University Hospital. The recording cuts off at the end.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR197)
    - Side A
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington (part 4), circa 1940-1949
        John Herling (narrator) explains why miners are at the hospital for treatment, and the role of the miners welfare fund in making it possible. See AFC 2003/011: SR196.
    - Side B
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [unidentified segment], circa 1940-1949
        Herling's narration continues. One of the patients, Rev. Archie Conway (Mann, WV), sings "A Coal Miner's Goodbye" (his own composition). Herling briefly interviews Korson. See AFC 2003/011: SR199b for the same recording.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR198)
    Man and woman sing a duet, accompanied by a banjo (?)
    - Side A
      - "I am a coal miner was born in Tennessee..."
    - Side B
      - "I work in the mines it's seventeen-fifty a day..."
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR199)
    - Side A
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [part 2], circa 1949-1952
        John Herling interviews Mr. Weaver (a miner at George Washington University Hospital).
    - Side B
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington (part 1), circa 1949-1952
        See AFC 2003/011: SR197b for the same recording.
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR200)
    Both songs performed by Dan Walsh (Centralia, Pennsylvania)
    - Side A
      - The Celebrated Workingman [sic]
    - Side B
      - The Shoefly [sic]
  - Sound recording (musical performance), 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR201)
    All songs performed by Jerry Byrne (Buck Run, Schuykill County, Pennsylvania). He announces the song as "When the breaker starts up on full-time."
    - Side A
      - When the breaker starts up full-time [sic]
      - Johnny's Mitchell's Train
    - Side B
      - Me Johnny Mitchell Man
      - The Hungarian Ball
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR202)
    - Side A
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [part 7], circa 1949-1952
        John Herling interviews miners who are patients at George Washington University Hospital. Includes a recording (copied from another source) of John L. Lewis testifying in a Congressional hearing.
    - Side B
      - Labor and the Nation: Mr. Coal Miner Goes to Washington [final segment], circa 1949-1952
        Continued from AFC 2003/011: SR202, Side A
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR203)
    - Side A
      - The Old Miner's Refrain
    - Side B
      - Down in the Coal Mines
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR204)
    - Side A
    - [Untitled]
      Dub of a commercial recording: a man sings a Christian song
      - Love Reasons [fragment]
        Unientified female singer, accompanied by guitar
      - Lord Rendall
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR205)
    - Side A
      - Love Reasons [fragment]
        Unientified female singer, accompanied by guitar. See AFC 2003/011: SR204 for the same recording.
      - Lord Rendall
    - Side B
      - [Untitled]
        Narrator begins a description of three frescoes dedicated to Carl Sandburg, and begins to recite a poem. The recording cuts off abruptly.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR206)
    Dub of a radio program. Christian songs performed by an unidentified man. Titles supplied by the AFC processor.
    - Side A
      - Every Valley Shall be Exalted
      - Side B
    - Open the Gates of the Temple
      - I Know that My Redeemer Liveth
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR207)
    See note for AFC 2003/011: SR198.
    - Side A
      - "I am a coal miner was born in Tennessee..."
    - Side B
      - "I work in the mines it's seventeen-fifty a day..."
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR208)
    Unidentified male performer, accompanied by guitar. Titles on Side B provided by the AFC processor.
    - Side A
      - The Wreck of the Cheverolet 34
        The singer introduces the song by saying it is from the singing of Leith [?] Parker, sung to the tune of "The Wreck of the C & O Number Five."
    - Side B
      - Streets of Laredo
      - The Erie Canal
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR209)
    Possibly a dub of other sound disc recordings. All songs performed by Jerry Byrne.
    - Side A
      - Me Johnny Mitchell Man
      - The Hungarian Ball
    - Side B
      - When the Breaker Starts Up on Full-Tme
      - Johnny Mitchell's Train
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR210)
    - Side A
      - The Shoofly
    - Side B
      - A Celebrated Workingman
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR211)
    Both songs performed by Dan Walsh
    - Side A
      - The Old Miner's Refrain
    - Side B
      - Down in the Coal Mines
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR212)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
        Unidentified man singing and playing guitar.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR213)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
        Recording of music on the radio or played on a phonograph, with someone humming along.
      - I Wonder If They All Get Home Tonight
        Performed by Paul Prichard [?]; a humorous version of "I Wonder How the Old Folks Are At Home."
      - [Untitled]
        A woman and child speak.
    - Side B
      - Better Run, Bill Green
        Performed by United Four Quartet [?]
      - I Can Tell the World What the Union Has Done
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR214)
    All songs performed in Spanish by Eduardo Gallegos (coal miner from Albuquerque, NM), with guitar accompaniment
    - Side A
      - [Unidentified]
      - El Minerito (The Little Miner)
        Composed by Eduardo Gallegos
    - Side B
      - El Minerito (The Little Miner)
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR215)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
        An undentified man recites part of a poem.
      - [Untitled]
        Possibly part of a radio soap opera, music clips, etc.
    - Side B
      - The Collier's Dying Child
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR216)
    - Side A
      - Mi Mulita (My Little Mule)
        Performed in Spanish by Eduardo Gallegos, with guitar accompaniment
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR217)
    - Side A
      - My Love Is a Mule in the Mine
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR218)
    - Side A
      - I Wonder If They All Get Home Tonight
        See note for AFC 2003/011: SR213.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR219)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
        An unidentified girl recites a series observations and requests. Possibly recorded from the radio.
    - Side B
      - [Untitled]
        Recorded from one or more radio shows on NBC. Segments include a poem recited by Betsy Korson.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 8 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR220)
    Both sides were recorded from one or more radio shows. Segments include poetry recited by Betsy Korson.
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 8 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR221)
    - Side A
      - [Untitled]
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 8 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR222)
    Both sides were recorded from one or more radio shows. Segments include spoken-word performances by Betsy Korson.
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR223)
    Recorded from a children's radio show on NBC. Segments include poetry recited by Betsy Korson.
  - Sound recording, on 1 side of 1 sound disc (lacquer on aluminum): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR224)
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR225)
    - Side A
      - Down, Down, Down
        Introduced by Bill Keating; sung by "the chorus" (a men's chorus), with soloists taking turns.
    - Side B
      - When the Breaker Starts Up Full Time
        Performed the Welsh Male Chorus; the soloist is Thomas C. Roberts.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR226)
    - Side A
      - Sweet Adeline [fragment]
        Sung by an unidentified man, to humorous effect.
      - [Untitled], December 1941
        Part of a radio broadcast, presumed to be about the attack on Pearl Harbor.
      - [Untitled]
        Possibly various brief segments of radio shows.
    - Side B
      - [Untitled]
        George, Rae, and Betsy Korson record a message for a young relative named Brucie. Another man introduces them, possibly Brucie's father.
  - Sound recording, 1 sound disc (lacquer): analog; 10 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR227)
    - Side A
      - Casey at the Bat